A Guide to the Vice-President for Administration Office Administrative Files, 1985-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Vice-President for Administration Office Administrative Files 1985-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.911
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1991 August 26.
Contents List
- Series I: General Files
  - Administration--General 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing--Major Systems Development Requests 1988 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing--General 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Aircraft Transportation--General 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Albemarle Housing Coalition 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Assistant V.P. for Business and Finance 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Associate Provost for Research 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Auditor's Office 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Athletic Department, UVa. 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Auxiliary Services 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Blandy Farm 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors--General 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors (4 folders) 1987 Oct-1988 Mar (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors--Audit Committee 1988 March 17-18 (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors--Briefing for New Committee Members 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors--Finance Committee 1988 May 10 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors--Darden, Joshua P., Jr. (Itinerary--Facilities Tour) 1987 June 30 (Box 2)
  - Visitors--Security Measures 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Budget Office--General 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Budget (Operating) 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Budget Addendum 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Budget--Maintenance Reserve Calculations 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Capital Outlay Budget Program, 1988-1998 1986-1988 (Box 2)
  - Capital Budget Programs, 1988-1990 1984-1988 (Box 2)
  - Capital Outlay Plan, 1990-2000 1988 (Box 2)
  - Capital Budget Programs 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Capital Outlay Review 1987 Nov 20 (Box 2)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Center for Study of Higher Education 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce--General 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce--Board of Directors 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce--Business/Education Partnership 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce--Leadership 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Charlottesville, City of--General 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Charlottesville, City of--Dept. of Community Development 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Charlottesville, City of--Minority Business 1988 (Box 2)
  - Charlottesville, City of--Traffic Study: Downtown/W. Main 1988 (Box 2)
  - Citizens Committee for City/County Cooperation (CCCCC) 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Clinch Valley College--General 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate. School of Business Administration 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Commerce School--General 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Communications Service 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Comptroller's Office 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Students 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Education, School of 1988 (Box 3)
  - Employee Health Services 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Engineering and Applied Sciences 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Environmental Health and Safety Office 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs--General 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Forum 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Employee Communication Council 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Focus on Research 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Focus on Research--Biology 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Focus on Research--Chemistry 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Focus on Research--Physics 1987 (Box 3)
  - Focus on Research--Psychology 1988 (Box 3)
  - Focus on Research--Science Dept. Chairs 1987 (Box 3)
  - Hospital Foundation 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - General Services--General 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Governmental Relations--General 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Governmental Relations--Non-Budgetary Amendments 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Historic Districts--General 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Housing Division 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Institutional Planning--AAUDE Meeting 1988 (Box 3)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Planning and Coordination Council--JPA/Fontaine Avenue Study 1987 (Box 4)
  - Jefferson Area Board for Aging 1988 (Box 4)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration Advisory Board 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Joint Dispatch Center--911 System (General) 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) 1986 (Box 4)
  - Law School 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Legal Adviser's Office 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--General 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--Axselle Meeting in Richmond 1987 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--CAPPS 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management Compliance Audit 1987 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--Inventory Management System 1987 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--Procurement Issues 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Procurements and Foundations 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--Radiology Audit 1987 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--Radiology Gift Solicitation 1987 (Box 4)
  - Medical Center--General 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Neighborhood Associations--General 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Parking and Transportation Services 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Personnel--General 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Personnel--Process for Hiring Wage Employees 1987 (Box 4)
  - Personnel--Smoking Ordinance 1988 (Box 4)
  - Personnel--Suggestion Awards Program 1987 (Box 4)
  - Physical Plant-General (2 folders) 1986-1988 (Box 5)
  - Physical Plant--Asbestos Removal 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Physical Plant--Birdwood 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Physical Plant--Complaints 1987 (Box 5)
  - Physical Plant--meeting with Middleton and Bouchard re: turn-over 1988 (Box 5)
  - Physical Plant--Mitch Van Yahres Meeting 1987 Dec 30 (Box 5)
  - City Planning Commission 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - County Planning Commission 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Police Department--General 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Police Department--Board of Visitors 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Gardens Policy 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Policy File 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Policies on the Lawn 1985-1987 (Box 5)
  - President's Office--General 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - President's Office--Commencement 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - President's Office--Harris Corporation 1987 (Box 6)
  - President's Office--National Public Service Awards 1987 (Box 6)
  - President's Administrative Roundtable 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - President's Office--Staff Meeting 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Printing and Mail Service 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Provost Office 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Risk Management--General 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Route 29 North 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Route 29 North 1988 (Box 6)
  - General--Space Management Organization 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Student Affairs 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Student Council 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Student Council--Sharing Charlottesville 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - University Real Estate Foundation 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - VP for Business and Finance 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - VP for Health Affairs 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - West Virginia University 1988 (Box 7)
- Series II: Committees:
  - Arboretum and Landscape Committee 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Task Force on Afro-American Affairs 1986-1988 (Box 7)
  - Chapel Committee 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Cemetery Committee--Columbarium 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Computing and Communications Committee 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Child Care (3 folders) 1988 (Box 7)
  - Child Care Task Force--October, November, December 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Child Care Task Force--July, August, September 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Child Care Committee (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Gift and Furnishings Task Force--General 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Graphics Committee 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Handicap Advisory Committee 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Master Plan Committee--General 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Master Plan--North Grounds 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Master Plan--Parking and Transportation Goals and Objectives 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Security and General Safety Committee 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Sexual Assault Task Force 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Status of Women Task Force 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Space Management Task Force 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - University Space Study 1988 (Box 9)
  - Special Project Committee ($10,000) 1987 (Box 9)
  - Task Force on Use of University Resources 1987 (Box 9)